(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
鷹嶺ルイ 重大告知 LIVE
Takane Lui Major Announcement LIVE
TAKANE LUI
3D LIVE
NEXT CHAPTER
holoX Executives
Lapis Lazuli
四六時中 界隈の徘徊で
Wandering the neighborhood around the clock,
面倒臭さを押し付けられてる
Having all the hassle forced onto me,
何から何まで
From this to that, everything.
思考を止めて また都合良くなる
Stop thinking and it becomes convenient again,
聞くを上手に頷き合ってる
Skillfully listening and nodding along,
仲良しこよしで
Pretending to be good friends.
さあ ダダダダ 黙れ黙りたまえよ
Now, shut up, shut up, just shut your mouth!
言えないない そんな強い言葉は
I can't, I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね
I just want you to be a little quiet.
あー 私たち 逮捕へ
Ah, we are heading for arrest!
社会 敵・敵・敵 プクヤヤヤ
Society is full of enemies, enemies, enemies, Puku-yayaya!
果たすその日まで
Until the day we fulfill it.
ララララ 獄 ヤヤヤ
La-la-la-la, prison, yayaya!
あの世の棒にも ヤヤヤ
Even a stick in the afterlife, yayaya!
社会 敵・敵・敵 好かれ合い愛
Society is enemies, enemies, enemies, loving each other,
約束の地まで
Until we reach the promised land.
さあ カキクケコ 待ってん待ってん
Now, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, waiting, waiting,
てててて 毒 ヤヤヤ
Te-te-te-te, poison, yayaya!
今日も来ない
You're not coming today either,
そっちの気だね
I guess that's how you feel.
いいえ 寝るから
No, I'm going to sleep,
私一人でもやっておきますね
So I'll just do it by myself.
全て 全て
Everything, everything,
全て任せて
Leave everything to me,
それをさせてよ
Let me do that.
あたしのことなの
It's about me,
分かっているでしょ
You understand, right?
四六時中 界隈の徘徊で
Wandering the neighborhood around the clock,
面倒臭い まま
Remaining troublesome,
今日も明日も過ぎて行くのでしょう
Today and tomorrow will probably just pass by.
みんなー！今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thanks for coming today!
やったー！
Yay!
一緒に歌ってたよ！
We sang together!
楽しい！
So fun!
いぇーい！
Yeah!
花瓶に水をあげましょう
Let's water the vase.
時の中 萎れたこと
I forgot that it had withered
忘れてた
within the passage of time.
さあ ダダダダ 黙れ黙りたまえよ
Now, shut up, shut up, just shut your mouth!
言えないない そんな強い言葉は
I can't, I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね
I just want you to be a little quiet.
あー 私たち 逮捕へ
Ah, we are heading for arrest!
今と未来
The present and the future...
見たかったはずなのに
I was supposed to want to see them.
社会 敵・敵・敵 プクヤヤヤ
Society is full of enemies, enemies, enemies, Puku-yayaya!
見えぬその日まで
Until that unseen day.
ドドドド 毒 ヤヤヤ
Do-do-do-do, poison, yayaya!
この世の理 ヤヤヤ
The logic of this world, yayaya!
今は セセセセ プク サササ
Now, se-se-se-se, puku-sasasa!
あなたの間違い
Your mistake.
片付くのはバッテンさ
Getting it tidied up is an X (fail).
社会 敵・敵・敵 プクヤヤヤ
Society is full of enemies, enemies, enemies, Puku-yayaya!
果たすその日まで
Until the day we fulfill it.
レレレレ 獄 ヤヤヤ
Le-le-le-le, prison, yayaya!
あの世の棒にも ヤヤヤ
Even a stick in the afterlife, yayaya!
社会 敵・敵・敵 好かれ合い愛
Society is enemies, enemies, enemies, loving each other,
約束の地まで
Until we reach the promised land.
さあ カキクケコ 待ってん待ってん
Now, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko, waiting, waiting,
てててて 尽くし並び
Te-te-te-te, lined up with devotion,
天 地 ノ ワ イ を開けましょう
Let's open the Heaven, Earth, and No-Why!
もういいじゃん 向きになっちゃって
Enough already, getting all serious.
カッコつけて カッコよくない
Acting cool but it's not cool at all.
そういうの嫌になってんだ
I'm getting sick of that kind of stuff.
放っといてよ 死にたくない
Leave me alone, I don't want to die.
もういいじゃん ヤケになってんの
Enough already, are you getting desperate?
嫉妬したり じっとできない
Getting jealous, can't sit still.
聞こえないよう 耳塞いだって
Even if I cover my ears so I can't hear,
入ってくるじゃん しんどいな
It still gets in, it's so exhausting.
僕は誰も望まないよ
I don't wish for anyone.
だから僕のこと そっとしておいて
So please, just leave me alone.
ウザい だけの馬鹿に はいはいはい
To the annoying idiots, yeah, yeah, yeah.
受ける またのぼせ待ってるね
Hilarious, you're getting carried away again.
だとか 本当は怯えてる
Saying that, but really I'm scared.
吠えるだけの弱虫だった
I was just a coward who could only bark.
痛い癖に耐えて はいはいはい
Enduring the pain, yeah, yeah, yeah.
いつも平気なふりばっかなの
Always just pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う
I laugh while keeping my walls up.
それ以上 近づかないでって
"Don't come any closer."
すごいじゃん
Amazing, huh?
ばかばっか
Just idiots.
やだ ばかばっか
No way, just idiots.
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの
Enough already, are you still angry?
放っといてよ 放っとできない
Leave me alone... I can't leave you alone.
見ないように目を逸らしたって
Even if I look away to avoid seeing,
ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
It follows me, after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん
If you fall, just get up.
失くしたなら探せばいいじゃん
If you lost it, just search for it.
いやいやいやいや
No, no, no, no.
それって良くない
That's not good.
間違ってたら直せばいいじゃん
If it's wrong, just fix it.
嫌だったら辞めればいいじゃん
If you hate it, just quit.
ボクは誰も覗かないよ
I won't peek at anyone.
だからボクのこと
So please, just...
ほっといて嫌なこと
...leave me alone.
全部大丈夫だと言えたら
If only I could say that all the bad things are fine,
いいのにな
that would be nice.
思えたらいいのにな
If only I could think that way.
違う予定調和な大正解
No, that pre-established harmony is the big correct answer.
いつもボクはそんなロールなの
I'm always stuck in that role.
また言いたいこと殺す
I kill what I want to say again.
だからもう忘れてくれ
So just forget about it already.
うわっはっは
Wah haha!
歌うだけのバカにハイハイハイ
Yes, yes, yes to the idiot who just sings.
受ける またどこ閉まってるね
Hilarious. You're closed off somewhere again, huh?
だとか本当は怯えてる
Or saying you're actually scared,
吠えるだけの弱虫だった
just a coward who only knows how to bark.
痛い口に耐えてハイハイハイ
Enduring the painful words, yes, yes, yes.
いつも平気なふりばっかなの
Always just pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う
I laugh while keeping my walls up.
それ以上近づかないで
Don't come any closer than that.
本当バカばっか
Truly, just a bunch of idiots.
いい加減ばっか
Just full of irresponsibility.
富んだバグばっか出せばって
Spitting out nothing but rich bugs.
そんな言葉っか
Just words like that.
もう僕もやっぱ
I guess I'm also...
どうしようもないんだった
...hopeless after all.
天井階 際の際立ってらんないない
Top floor, on the edge, can't stand out.
死ねるって僕も口ばっかだね
Saying 'I could die', I'm all talk too, huh?
今日も壁を張ったまま笑う
Today too, I laugh while keeping my walls up.
それ以上近づかないで
Don't come any closer than that.
怖いじゃん バカばっか
It's scary, isn't it? Just a bunch of idiots.
ホラ バカばっか
See, just a bunch of idiots.
はいということで！
Okay, so!
重大告知ライブ始まりましたー！
The Major Announcement Live has started!
みなさん待ったかね？
Did you all wait?
ホロックスの女幹部 鷹嶺ルイと申します
I am HoloX's executive officer, Takane Lui.
ということで みんな見えとるぞコメント
I can see everyone's comments!
あ、拍手いっぱいありがとな
Oh, thanks for all the applause.
拍手いっぱいありがとう
Thank you for the applause.
ということで 本日のハッシュタグはですね
So, today's hashtag is...
こちら！ あ、こっちにありますね
This one! Oh, it's over here.
えー #鷹嶺ルイ重大告知LIVE で
Uh, #TakaneLuiMajorAnnouncementLIVE,
たくさんつぶやいて...あ、つぶやきじゃないわ
please tweet a lot... Ah, not tweet.
ポストしてくれると嬉しいです
I'd be happy if you posted about it.
みんな今すぐポストしてくださーい
Everyone, please post right now!
ということで もう一曲目二曲目とね
So, with the first and second songs,
OverD、ばかばっかと熱い曲が続いたんですけれども
we had hot songs like 'OverD' and 'Bakabakka' in a row,
一曲目からなんと
but believe it or not, from the very first song,
特別ゲストが登場してくださいました
a special guest has appeared!
ちょっとね おしゃべりしたいと思いますので呼びたいと思います
I'd like to chat a bit, so I'll call her out.
べーちゃん！
Bae-chan!
あれ？あれあれ？
Huh? Huh, huh?
来たー！
She's here!
Wassup!
我はカオス！我の果て the End!
I am Chaos! My end, the End!
これのインフルエンサー 一種の黒狩の薔薇 汝の友
This influencer, a kind of black hunting rose, thy friend,
ホロの箱 Baelz です！
Holo's box, Baelz!
Fooo!
ということで べーちゃんとはね OverDを一緒に歌わせていただいたんですけれども
So, I got to sing 'OverD' together with Bae-chan.
めっちゃ嬉しい
I'm so happy!
嬉しい 私も嬉しい べーちゃんとは 本当にあの 一緒に歌いたくて
I'm happy too! I really wanted to sing with you, Bae-chan.
同じです
Same here.
え 嬉しい
Eh, I'm glad!
いや ルイ姉の曲 めっちゃ好きなんで 僕も
No, I really love your songs, Lui-nee. Me too.
え 嬉しい
Eh, so happy!
めっちゃかっこよくて
They are so cool.
いや やっと歌えましたね
Yeah, we finally got to sing together.
歌えました
We did.
なんかOverD 絶対べーちゃんに合うと思って
I thought 'OverD' would definitely suit you, Bae-chan.
やっぱカオスなんでね
Since it's Chaos, after all.
ははは
Hahaha.
いやめっちゃかっこいい
It was so cool.
いや嬉しい 一緒に歌えて
I'm so happy we could sing together.
ちょっとね あの最後のとこ ちょっとやらかした
Just... that last part, I kinda messed up.
え 嘘？
Eh, really?
全然分かんなかったよ 多分
I totally didn't notice. Probably.
いや 多分ね フリはね...言っていいこれ？
No, probably, the choreography... can I say this?
いいよ
Sure.
フリは元々なかったんだよね
There wasn't any choreography originally.
うんうんうん でなんかリハ中で
Right, right. And during rehearsal,
あ ちょっとフリつけようか みたいな話になってて
we were like, 'Should we add some moves?'
え え ヤバイ で ちょっと最後のとこ忘れちゃって すいません
And I was like 'Uh, oh no' and forgot the last part. Sorry.
いや全然全然全然 全然分からなかった
No, not at all! I didn't notice at all.
もうやっぱりさ テンション上がっちゃうとね
Well, you know, when the excitement goes up.
分かる！
I know right!
いやでも楽しんでくれたんだよね きっとね
But you enjoyed it, didn't you? Surely.
めっちゃ楽しい
It was so fun!
え 嬉しい
Eh, I'm glad!
めちゃくちゃ楽しい
So incredibly fun.
いや私もべーちゃんの曲 本当に大好きで
I really love your songs too, Bae-chan.
もういつかべーちゃんの曲も挑戦したいななんて
I'd love to try singing your songs someday.
え 是非是非聴きたい 聴きたい
Eh, please do! I want to hear it!
え 一緒に歌ってくれますか？
Eh, will you sing with me?
いや もう是非です いやルイ姉の
Absolutely! I mean, Lui-nee's...
Psycho聴きたいかも
I might want to hear 'Psycho'.
Psychoね！
'Psycho', huh!
いやPsycho難しいけど え 是非
Well, 'Psycho' is difficult, but yes, definitely!
一緒に歌いましょう
Let's sing it together.
歌いましょう お願いします
Let's sing! Please.
お願いします
Please!
なんだこれ
What is this?
ということで え 21時半からですね 頃
So, uh, around 9:30 PM,
あ 21時半頃にですね
ah, around 9:30 PM,
え 重大告知を
uh, I will make the major announcement,
重大告知？
Major announcement?
はい させていただきますので
yes, I'll be doing that, so
もう少しお待ちいただけますと幸いです
I'd appreciate it if you could wait a little longer.
Big announcement at 9:30 PM JST!
Thank you!
Thank you a lot
いや 海外ニキもね 返事してくれるんじゃないかな
I think the overseas bros will reply too.
大丈夫かな
Will it be okay?
Yes!
ということで この後はですね
So, after this,
事前収録で来ていただいたゲストさんのパートになりますので
we'll move on to the segment with the guest who came for the pre-recording.
一緒に じゃあVTRのキューフリしてもいいですか？べーちゃん
Can we do the VTR cue together, Bae-chan?
Yap!
それではみなさん この後も楽しんでいってください
Alright everyone, please enjoy what's coming next!
せーの
Ready, and...
VTR
どうぞ！
go ahead!
単純で明快で簡単じゃない
It's simple and clear, but not easy.
まだ想像と妄想と偏見でWhy
Still judging with imagination, delusion, and prejudice, Why?
そりゃ完全な万全な設定じゃない
That's not a complete, flawless setup.
からかってくれないか
Won't you tease me a little?
外見と内面と偶像の不一致
The mismatch of appearance, inner self, and idol image.
この繊細さ敏感さ共有しよ
Let's share this delicacy and sensitivity.
ほら冷静な表情は実際ちょーハイ
Look, this calm expression is actually super high.
見つけてくれないか
Won't you find me?
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sis, let's put it away and go.
はいはい期待感 背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's shoulder the expectations and go.
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sis, let's put it away and go.
はいはい期待感 背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's shoulder the expectations and go.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
高嶺の花みたいに
Like a flower on a high peak,
扱っちゃ嫌
I don't want to be treated like that.
あのね 誰も彼も
You see, everyone and anyone...
鷲と勘違い
...mistakes me for an eagle.
驚きの目
Eyes of surprise.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
PONコツがちょい
Just having a little bit of clumsiness...
あるだけで親近感
...makes me feel relatable.
その際 その差異 その才
That occasion, that difference, that talent...
受け止めてよね
...accept them all, okay?
鷹嶺の未来 乾杯
A toast to Takane's future.
しっかりウォッチ
Watch closely.
合間You Know
In the intervals, You Know.
狩りとか苦手
I'm bad at hunting.
猛禽類ね
A bird of prey, right?
一見クールね
Looks cool at first glance.
意外とギャップ系
Surprisingly a 'gap' type.
イメージ大変身
Major image transformation.
OK?
大衆の感性って内臓じゃない
Public sensibility isn't internal organs.
配信界に騒乱も多々あろう
There may be many disturbances in the streaming world.
ただ正論や暴論の配信じゃない
It's not just a stream of sound arguments or crazy talk.
個人的見解的大正解
From a personal viewpoint, it's a huge correct answer.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
捕食しないさ
I won't prey on you.
だから怖がっちゃ嫌
So don't be scared.
ほらね 爪も 羽も
Look, claws and wings too...
お洒落に研いで
...sharpened stylishly.
隠しちゃいない
I'm not hiding them.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
観察眼がちょい
Just having a little observant eye...
あるだけで緊張感
...creates tension.
その際 その差異 その才
That occasion, that difference, that talent...
受け止めてよね
...accept them all, okay?
鷹嶺の未来 乾杯
A toast to Takane's future.
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sis, let's put it away and go.
はいはい期待感 背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's shoulder the expectations and go.
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sis, let's put it away and go.
はいはい期待感 背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's shoulder the expectations and go.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
高嶺の花みたいに
Like a flower on a high peak,
扱っちゃ嫌
I don't want to be treated like that.
あのね 誰も彼も
You see, everyone and anyone...
鷲と勘違い
...mistakes me for an eagle.
驚きの目
Eyes of surprise.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-Holo Hawk, it's Holo Hawk, but...
PONコツがちょい
Just having a little bit of clumsiness...
あるだけで親近感
...makes me feel relatable.
その際 その差異 その才
That occasion, that difference, that talent...
受け止めてよね
...accept them all, okay?
鷹嶺の未来
Takane's future...
乾杯
Cheers.
愛じゃん
It's love, isn't it?
鷹まる時代 乾杯
A toast to the rising era of hawks.
Ma-ka Ma-ka
Sorry
to be late
Do you remember me?
醒める目と目が合ったら
If our waking eyes meet,
きっと赤かった
It was surely red.
Nightmareも真っ赤っ赤だ
Even the nightmare is bright red.
それは Wink off Wink off
That is Wink off, Wink off.
右肩のButterfly
Butterfly on the right shoulder.
I'm crazyな台風の目
I'm the crazy eye of the typhoon.
Wink
Show down お目が高い
Show down, you have a discerning eye.
目に入れたって痛くないくらい
Enough that it wouldn't hurt even if I put it in my eye.
La la la la クチバシに
La la la la, on the beak,
Sweet Vengeance
憎しみならとっくに捨てた
If it's hatred, I threw it away long ago.
怖がってんの？
Are you scared?
あっそ
Hmph.
Don't let me down
Eyes on me now
まだまだ
Not yet.
遊ビナ
Play.
安全じゃないから？
Because it's not safe?
健全じゃないから？
Because it's not wholesome?
それがなんだ
So what?
Franticだね
It's Frantic, isn't it?
目には眼を
An eye for an eye.
La la la la la
Wink
Say la la la 赤裸々 Gimme
Say la la la, stark naked Gimme.
Wink
Say la la la 真っ赤っ赤だ
Say la la la, it's bright red.
Oh Eye Eye Eye
Want you で 倍眼
Want you, double payback.
My Eye Eye...
目にもの見せる My Eye Eye
I'll show you what I'm made of, My Eye Eye.
Wink off
目をつぶる半分で
With eyes half closed,
Make a Wink
有能が喧嘩上等
My talent is ready for a fight.
My god My god
禍々
So ominous.
ほらご覧 瞬く間に
Look now, in the blink of an eye,
My Eye Eye Eye'll kill you
My Eye Eye, I'll kill you.
Wink
後ろ指 指したいならお好きにどうぞ
If you want to point fingers behind my back, go ahead.
当方 当然 振り返らぬ所存で降臨在
I descend here with absolutely no intention of looking back.
お待たせ Suck out Suck out
Kept you waiting, Suck out, Suck out.
おさらば 恨み Cut Cut
Farewell, malice, Cut, Cut.
無礼講な断頭台で
At this free-for-all guillotine,
I'm coming back coming back coming back
目じゃない眼中にはない
You're nothing to me, not even in my sights.
善良じゃないだろう
It's not virtuous, right?
最良じゃないだろう
It's not the best, right?
それがどうしたんだ Franticだね
So what? You're frantic.
目には眼を
An eye for an eye,
歯には羽を
A wing for a tooth.
La La La La La
C'est la la vie
あぁ類は友を呼ぶ
Ah, birds of a feather flock together.
C'est la vie 羽ばたきを知るWink
C'est la vie, a wink that knows how to fly.
目が離せない
You can't look away,
完璧なWink
From this perfect wink.
赤裸々 Lovin' セキララ Gimme a Wink
Naked Lovin', nakedly Gimme a Wink.
Say La La Liar 真っ赤っ赤だ
Say La La Liar, you're bright red.
Oh Eye Eye I want you de
バイバイあそばせ
...bid you bye-bye.
目にもの見せる My Eye Eye
I'll show you what I'm made of, My Eye Eye.
もう目が離せない Eye Eye
You can't take your eyes off me anymore, Eye Eye.
魔眼ウインク
Demon Eye Wink.
I kill you
引けない
I can't back down,
なんてありえない
That's impossible,
後に引けない
There's no retreat,
むやみにひけらかさない Fly
Don't show it off unnecessarily, Fly.
いつも突然のハラハラ
Always sudden suspense,
火花散らせば命からがら
Sparks fly, barely escaping with our lives.
待ったなし 個別ダンシング
No waiting allowed, individual dancing,
知らぬが仏 ステップでかわしちゃうぜ
Ignorance is bliss, I'll dodge it with a step.
サラリーな社会が眠る頃に
When the salaried society is asleep,
パラリラ輩バックするコロニー
Noisy hooligans back up the colony.
不実もっと烈 表裏一体を
Insincerity grows intense, slipping through the two sides,
くぐり抜けて Let's go
Of the same coin, Let's go.
平日は Shoo be doo be do
Weekdays are Shoo be doo be do,
週末も Shoo be doo be do
Weekends are also Shoo be doo be do.
時にきつくハードに
Sometimes tight and hard,
時に平和なバードに
Sometimes like a peaceful bird.
今宵 ひみつのおしごと
Tonight, it's secret work.
綺羅煌々 狙って Bang ba bang
Glittering brightly, aiming Bang ba bang,
外さない クリア
I won't miss, Clear.
いざ堂々 目立って Run and gun
Now majestic, standing out, Run and gun,
未だに他に類を見ない
Still unparalleled by any other.
意気揚々 迫って Bang ba bang
In high spirits, approaching Bang ba bang,
悟られず カバー
Unnoticed, Cover.
Here we go yo 気取ってさあ出番
Here we go yo, putting on airs, it's showtime.
跡を濁さず Take off
Leaving no trace behind, Take off.
決して逃がさない
I'll never let you escape,
剥いた牙を抜くまで
Until I pull out your bared fangs.
決して穢さない
I'll never let it be defiled,
守る無二の看板
The unique reputation I protect.
行き止まりのない手回し Oh yeah
Endless preparation, Oh yeah.
お見舞いする後の祭り Oh yeah
Serving you up a regretful aftermath, Oh yeah.
響くヒールの音が お仕置きの合図
The sound of echoing heels is the signal for punishment.
誰も彼も Check my Hawk Eye
Everyone, anyone, Check my Hawk Eye.
年始から Shoo be doo be do
From the start of the year, Shoo be doo be do,
年末も Shoo be doo be do
To the end of the year, Shoo be doo be do.
お任せあれハンドリング
Leave the handling to me,
表に出せない後処理
The clean-up that can't be made public.
もとい ひみつのおしごと
Or rather, secret work.
綺羅煌々 狙って Bang ba bang
Glittering brightly, aiming Bang ba bang,
外さない クリア
I won't miss, Clear.
いざ堂々 目立って Run and gun
Now majestic, standing out, Run and gun,
しばしば類は友を呼ぶ
Often, birds of a feather flock together.
意気揚々 迫って Bang ba bang
In high spirits, approaching Bang ba bang,
悟られず カバー
Unnoticed, Cover.
Here we go yo 気取ってさあ出番
Here we go yo, putting on airs, it's showtime.
爪を剥き出し
Baring my claws,
Beat you
たかが稼業もどきと侮るのなら
If you look down on this as mere make-believe work,
タガが外れて容赦できなくなって
I'll lose control and won't show any mercy,
野放図 暴れ
An unrestrained rampage.
本音隠し弱音なんてすぐねんね
Hiding true feelings, whining goes straight to sleep.
混じり気ないハートビート 揺らすこの世界
This pure heartbeat shakes the world.
最果てまで届くよう鳴らした鐘
The bell I rang to reach the very end,
裏の裏まで頂いちゃおう
Let's take it all, even the deepest secrets.
綺羅煌々 狙って Bang ba bang
Glittering brightly, aiming Bang ba bang,
外さない クリア
I won't miss, Clear.
いざ堂々 目立って Run and gun
Now majestic, standing out, Run and gun,
未だに他に類を見ない
Still unparalleled by any other.
意気揚々 迫って Bang ba bang
In high spirits, approaching Bang ba bang,
悟られず カバー
Unnoticed, Cover.
Here we go yo 気取ってさあ出番
Here we go yo, putting on airs, it's showtime.
跡を濁さず Take off
Leaving no trace behind, Take off.
Shoo be do be do doo...
今日もひみつの Take off
Today too, a secret take off.
立派なこの羽根に
On these magnificent wings,
泥をつけて貼って剥がして
smearing mud, pasting and peeling.
理想 萎えた爪立てて
Digging in my withered claws of ideals,
信じられるものは
believing that the only thing
自分だけだと思い込んで
I could trust was myself,
進み続けた
I kept moving forward.
あの子みたいにすれば？
"Why not be like that girl?"
君じゃそれは無理だ
"That's impossible for you."
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say whatever they want.
だって独り 逆境の世紀
Because I'm alone in this century of adversity,
愛すら空回って
where even love spins in vain.
私の邪魔させやしない
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Like a Takane 見据えた神
Like a Takane, the god I gazed at.
穴蔵から空へ
From the burrow to the sky.
飛んでいく私を見ないなんて
How can you not watch me fly away?
Bad boy
失敗は止まった時
Failure is when you stop.
今日も挑み張っての
Today too, I'm challenging and striving.
意味のないものはないと
Believing there's nothing meaningless,
信じられるものを見つけ出すまで
until I find something I can believe in,
どんな日だって
no matter what kind of day it is,
笑い飛ばすんだ
I'll laugh it off.
Na ni na ni na Na ni na ni na
La la la ta rat ta ta
La la la la
あの子はもう終わりだ
"That girl is finished."
これ以上はないね
"She can't go any further."
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say whatever they want.
いつの日か 寝ても覚めても
Someday, awake or asleep,
夢見てた大歓声
that great applause I dreamed of...
私はここで死にたくない
I don't want to die here!
一緒の旅 逆境の世紀
A journey together in this century of adversity,
愛すら空回って
where even love spins in vain.
私の邪魔させやしない
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Like a Takane 見据えた神
Like a Takane, the god I gazed at.
穴蔵から空へ
From the burrow to the sky.
飛んでいく私を見ないなんて
How can you not watch me fly away?
Bad boy
Bad boy...
誰かに言われなくたって
Even if no one tells me,
私の方が もっと嫌いだ
I hate it more than anyone.
うるさいな
Shut up.
騒がしい視界を塞いで
Blocking the noisy view,
惨めな理由を書き連ねる
I list up miserable reasons.
教室にずっと居残り
Staying behind in the classroom forever,
窓の向こうに黒い影があって
there was a black shadow beyond the window,
何も言わずにこっちを見ていた
looking at me without saying a word.
私は貴方に救われたくて 泣くんじゃない
I'm not crying because I want to be saved by you.
産声は止められないもの
A first cry is something that cannot be stopped.
何千回ともう一度 死に損ないを
Thousands of times, and once more, surviving death,
希望と絶望の真ん中を纏って
wrapped in the middle of hope and despair.
醜い光を許したのは
The one who forgave the ugly light
他ならない私だった
was none other than myself.
息をして
Breathe.
目を開けて
Open your eyes.
これが最後かどうか
Whether this is the last time,
知る術はないよ
there's no way to know.
知りたくもないよ
I don't even want to know.
優しいな
It's so gentle...
コンコンと闇は寄り添って
Darkness snuggles up deeply,
解けない答えを塗り潰し
painting over the insoluble answer...
…もないよと
…there's nothing anymore.
窓を挟んで微かに聞こえた
I heard it faintly across the window.
それは祈るような啜り泣きだった
It was a sobbing sound like a prayer.
私は貴方を救える言葉を知らないけど
I don't know the words to save you, but...
寂しいねって声をかけた
I called out, saying 'It's lonely, isn't it.'
何千回ともう一度 死に損ないを
Thousands of times and once more, the survivor.
希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Clad in the midnight of hope and despair.
何千回ともう一度 生きる貴方へ
Thousands of times and once more, to you who lives.
私も続くよ 窓の向こう側で
I will follow too, on the other side of the window.
醜い光を愛してた時
When I loved the ugly light,
終わらせなかった産声を
The first cry that I didn't let end...
歌にしよう
Let's make it a song.
特報
Special News
戦う理由は、一つじゃない
The reason to fight is not just one.
Takane Lui 2nd Album Lapis Lazuli
2025.12.03
全国CDショップにて予約開始！
Pre-orders start at CD shops nationwide!
GAMERSにてリリース記念ミニライブ開催決定！
Release commemorative mini-live to be held at GAMERS!
Stay Tuned.
はい ということで
Okay, so...
今 特報を見ていただきましたが
You just watched the special news, but...
なんと！鷹嶺ルイ 12月3日に
Believe it or not! Takane Lui, on December 3rd,
自身のセカンドアルバム『Lapis Lazuli』を
her own second album 'Lapis Lazuli'...
発売することが決定しました！
has been decided for release!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ということで なんとですね 今回は
So, surprisingly, this time,
鷹嶺史上初の全国…
Takane's first ever nationwide...
全国のショップで買える 全国流通盤ということで
available at shops nationwide, a nationwide distribution edition!
また一つ夢が叶っちゃいました
Another dream has come true.
みんなのおかげです ありがとう！
It's thanks to everyone. Thank you!
ファーストに続きまして『Liberty』に続きまして セカンドなんですけれども
Following the first, following 'Liberty', it's the second, but...
今回は『Lapis Lazuli』というね タイトルをつけさせていただきました
This time, I've given it the title 'Lapis Lazuli'.
この『Lapis Lazuli』というのはですね
This 'Lapis Lazuli' is...
いつも あの アルバムには『L』の文字がついてるんですけれども
Usually, my albums have the letter 'L' attached to them,
今回も『L』の文字から始まる『Lapis Lazuli』という言葉で
but this time too, with 'Lapis Lazuli' starting with 'L',
こちらですね あの 意味がですね
this one, the meaning is...
成功に導くだったりとか
like leading to success, or...
あとは結構 あの 勝利へと 勝利を掴み取るみたいな
also, it's quite like towards victory, or grabbing victory,
意味合いが込められておりまして
such meanings are included.
なんとこちらアルバムはですね 『VS』 戦いをテーマにした曲になっております
Surprisingly, this album consists of songs with the theme of 'VS', battle.
あ 曲が 曲ばかりになっておりますので
Ah, it's full of songs like that, so...
そういった意味合いも込めて 『Lapis Lazuli』という名前をつけさせていただきました
including those meanings, I named it 'Lapis Lazuli'.
さらになんとですね！
Furthermore, believe it or not!
秋葉原ゲーマーズ本店さんでも
At the Akihabara Gamers Main Store as well...
リリース記念ライブをやらせていただくことになりました！
I will be holding a release commemorative live!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんと ミニライブも開催ということで
Surprisingly, a mini-live will also be held, so...
え 本日ですね え 12時半から予約開始となっているので もう
Uh, today, uh, pre-orders started from 12:30, so already...
すでに え 予約ができる状態になっております
it is already in a state where you can pre-order.
え みなさんもう見えますかね？
Uh, can everyone see it already?
え 画面の左下
Uh, the bottom left of the screen.
左下にボタンありますか？
Is there a button on the bottom left?
みんなある？ボタン
Does everyone have it? The button.
あるかしら
I wonder if it's there.
そこからですね 購入ボタンがありますので そこから予約ができるように
From there, there is a purchase button, so you can pre-order from there...
なりましたので ぜひぜひこちらから予約してみてください
so please, by all means, try pre-ordering from here.
ということでアルバムの詳細をね え バーッとお話させていただこうかなと思うんですけれども
So, I think I'd like to quickly talk about the details of the album, but...
おめでとう ありがとう みんな
Congratulations, thank you everyone.
え 収録曲については こちらになります デデン
Uh, regarding the recorded songs, it becomes this. Ta-da.
はい え 先行リリースしております『Zig-Zag』をはじめ
Yes, uh, starting with 'Zig-Zag' which has been released in advance,
え 先ほども言いました『VS』 戦いをテーマにした全10曲が収録されています
uh, as I said earlier, all 10 songs with the theme of 'VS', battle, are recorded.
え 6曲目にはですね みなさんお分かりですか？フィーチャリング ラプラス・ダークネスということで
Uh, for the 6th song, do you all understand? It's featuring La+ Darknesss, so...
一緒に歌った曲も収録はされております。
A song we sang together is also recorded.
そしてですね、色々まぁ、言いたいことはあるんですけども、
And, well, there are many things I want to say, but...
一つ一つ言いたいんですけども、ちょっとお時間がないので、
I want to talk about each one, but since we don't have much time...
えー、10曲目の『抗うキミへのレクイエム』という曲はですね、
Um, the 10th song, 'Requiem for the Resisting You'...
とあるアニメのイメージソングになっておりますので、
is actually an image song for a certain anime, so...
これから色々情報が出てくると思いますので、
I think various information will be coming out from now on, so...
えー、楽しみに待っていただければなと思います。
please look forward to it.
そして！完全生産限定盤はこんな感じに…なっております。どうぞ！
And! The fully limited production edition looks like... this. Here!
お、どうぞ。あ、こっちだ。どうぞ。あ、こっちだ。(笑)
Oh, here. Ah, this way. Here. Ah, this way. (Laughs)
えー、スライドボックス式でですね、あの…
Um, it's a slide box style, and, um...
2人の鷹嶺ルイを、あの、離したりくっついたりできる。
You can, um, separate or join the two Takane Luis.
オシャレでしょ？
Stylish, right?
しかも『Liberty』と同じ、SOLANIさんが、えー、イラストを担当してくださいました。
Plus, just like with 'Liberty', SOLANI-san was in charge of the illustration.
めちゃくちゃカッコよくないですか？ぜひぜひね。
Isn't it super cool? Please, by all means...
あの、戦わせたり離したりして、遊んでみてください。
um, try playing with it by making them fight or separating them.
他にも、このようなグッズもございます。
There are also other goods like these.
完全生産限定盤にはですね、えー、今までのリリースした楽曲のジャケットを…
In the fully limited production edition, um, the jackets of the songs released so far...
えー、入れ込んだ、ジャケットイラストブック。これね、私が欲しいって言ったんですよ。
are compiled into a jacket illustration book. This, you see, I said I wanted it.
そしたらね、む、無理やり欲しいって言ったんですけど、
And then, well, I forcefully said I wanted it, but...
なんと実現をしてくださいまして、今までの…
surprisingly, they made it happen! The past...
えー、リリース、リリースした楽曲のジャケットが1冊の本になって見れる…
um, release... released song jackets can be seen as a single book...
やつになっております。
is what it has become.
いやみんな欲しかったでしょ？
Everyone wanted this, right?
いや、私が欲しいものはきっとみんなが欲しいと思いまして…
No, I thought that what I want is surely what everyone wants...
えー、こちらちょっとむ、無理やりに作っていただきました。
so, um, I kind of forced them to make this.
ご協力してくださったあの関係者の皆さんありがとうございます。
Thank you to all the staff who cooperated.
そしてですね、オリジナル缶バッジも2種類ついて…
And also, two types of original can badges are included...
そしてそして、今回もですね、完全生産限定盤に、だけになるんですけれども…
And, and! This time too, although it's only for the fully limited production edition...
直筆サイン入りジャケットカードを、購入者全員！皆さんに！
a handwritten signed jacket card, for all purchasers! Everyone!
えー、直筆サインさせていただきますので…
Um, I will sign each one by hand, so...
ぜひぜひ、完全生産限定盤、色んな特典がありますので買っていただけますと幸いでございます。
please, by all means, buy the fully limited production edition as it has many benefits, I would be happy.
さらに、通常盤はこちら。
Furthermore, here is the regular edition.
はい、通常盤にはですね、ランダムアナザージャケット…
Yes, in the regular edition, a random another jacket...
えー、1枚入り。えー、全5種類ある中の1枚が入っております。
um, one included. Um, one out of five types is included.
そして、こちらもですね、数量限定ランダムで鷹嶺ルイの直筆サイン、そして！
And, for this one too, in limited quantities, randomly, Takane Lui's handwritten sign, and!
コメントもついてきます。直筆コメントもついてきます。
A comment is also included. A handwritten comment is also included.
ちょっとこちらはランダムになっちゃうんですけれども…
This one ends up being random, but...
ぜひぜひ、あ、皆さんに当たりますように。
I really hope, ah, that you all get one.
通常盤もぜひ買ってみてください。
Please buy the regular edition too.
そしてそして、各ショップの、えー、法人特典はこちらになります。ドドン。
And, and! The corporate benefits for each shop are here. Dodon!
Amazonさんマウスパッドだったり、色々なね、えー、お店で…
Mouse pads at Amazon, and at various, um, stores...
色んな特典がついておりますので…
various benefits are included, so...
皆さん欲しいものがあれば、そちらで予約してくださると嬉しいでございます。
if there's something you want, I'd be happy if you pre-ordered there.
また詳細などは、えー、ポストしますので…
Also, I will post the details later, so...
そちらで詳しく見ていてください。
please check the details there.
はい！さらに、こちら！
Yes! Furthermore, this!
えー、先ほどもお伝えしました、秋葉原ゲーマーズ本店さんにて…
Um, as I mentioned earlier, at the Akihabara Gamers Main Store...
12月7日に、リリース記念ミニライブの開催が決定しました！
on December 7th, the release commemorative mini-live event has been decided!
ゲーマーズさんでアルバムを購入した人の中から抽選で…
From those who purchased the album at Gamers, by lottery...
ミニライブにご招待をさせていただきます。
we will invite you to the mini-live.
ぜひ、ゲーマーズさんでもアルバムを買ってくださると嬉しいでございます。
I would be happy if you bought the album at Gamers too.
ということで、えー、今回ですね…
So, um, this time...
あの、皆さんの左下にあるボタンではですね、完全生産盤と通常盤のところにECサイトに飛ぶのかな？
um, with the button on your bottom left, does it jump to the EC site for the fully limited and regular editions?
多分オフィシャルサイトに飛びますので、えー、皆さんそちらで…
It probably jumps to the official site, so, um, everyone, there...
完全生産盤だったりとかが欲しいよっていう方はそちらで、えー、予約をしていただきまして…
those who want the fully limited edition, etc., please pre-order there...
ちょっと他の、えー、ショップさんで予約をしたいよという方はね、あの、詳細…
those who want to pre-order at other shops, well, um, the details...
後ほど、あの、X、そして概要欄にも貼らせていただきますので…
later, um, I will post on X, and paste it in the description, so...
そちらでチェックをしていただけると嬉しいでございます。
I would be happy if you checked there.
いやラピスラズリ…しかもですね、ちょっとラピスラズリって…
Well, Lapis Lazuli... and also, you know, Lapis Lazuli is...
あの、誕生月？誕生石？が9月と12月ということで…
um, the birth month? Birthstone? Is September and December, so...
なんと9月にわたくし重大発表をして…
surprisingly, I made a major announcement in September...
12月に発売っていうね…
and it goes on sale in December...
あ、これたまたまなんですけど、あ、まぁたまたまって言わない方がいいよね…
Ah, this is a coincidence, but, ah, maybe I shouldn't say it's a coincidence...
あ、これね、あの、しか、仕掛けなんですね、これ。
Ah, this, um, is a tr-trick, you see, this.
仕掛けさせていただきました。
I set it up.
ぐ、偶然、偶然じゃなくて、ちゃん、ちゃんと、ちゃんとえー考えました。
Co-coincidence, it's not a coincidence, I pro-properly... I properly thought about it.
ぜひ皆さん ご購入いただけますと幸いです
I would be happy if you could purchase it.
よろしくお願いします
Thank you very much.
それでは まだまだ歌っていきたいと思います
Well then, I'd like to keep singing.
この後も まだまだ告知がございますので
There are still more announcements coming up after this,
お楽しみに
so please look forward to it.
ちょっとお水を飲んでもいいですか？
Can I drink some water?
お水飲んでもいいですね
I can drink water, right?
お水飲みます
I'm drinking water.
ちょっと待ってください
Please wait a moment.
飲みました
I drank it.
ということで
So,
まだお一人 ゲストが出てない方がいらっしゃいますね
there's still one guest who hasn't appeared yet, right?
その方はいつ出るんでしょうか
When will that person appear?
お見逃しなく
Don't miss it.
ということで 続いての曲
So, with that said, the next song...
行きましょうか
shall we go?
皆さん準備は大丈夫ですか？
Is everyone ready?
準備は大丈夫ですね
You're ready, right?
それでは
Alright then,
はい それでは聴いてください
yes, please listen.
ジグザグ
ZIG-ZAG.
One two three four
ということで！
So!
もう一人の特別ゲストを呼びたいと思います
I'd like to call the other special guest!
星街すいせい！
Hoshimachi Suisei!
盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get hyped!
幸せ です ささやいた
Happiness, you whispered.
問いがラッタタラッタ こびりついて離れはダメだ
The question goes rattattaratta, stuck to me, leaving is no good.
ラッタッタラッタ
Rattattaratta.
無味無臭の生活が思い出せないや
I can't remember my odorless, tasteless life.
忘れたいから歌った
I sang because I wanted to forget.
馬鹿だ ラッタッタラッタ
I'm an idiot, rattattaratta.
羨むことも
Envying,
憎むことも
and hating,
賢くないゆえ出来なかった
I couldn't do it because I wasn't smart.
これが君の結末ならば
If this is your ending,
笑ってしまいたいほど
enough to make me want to laugh.
嘘 嘘 嘘
Lie, lie, lie.
嘘つき
Liar.
やだ 痛い 痛い 痛い 痛いな
No, it hurts, hurts, hurts, hurts.
奇跡とかちょっと望んじゃって
Hoping a little for a miracle,
もう嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
I already hate, hate, hate, hate, hate it.
たちが悪いは
It's nasty.
ねぇ 辛い 辛い 辛い 辛いな
Hey, it's painful, painful, painful, painful.
お菓子とか全部えぐり取って
Scoop out all the sweets,
薄情で結構
Cold-hearted is fine,
好きに呼んでいいよ
call me whatever you like.
トラウマにバイバイしたいのです です
I want to say bye-bye to trauma, desu desu.
ででっでっです
De-de-de-desu.
私 甘え上手になれなかった
I couldn't become good at relying on others.
可愛げとかが足りなかった
I lacked cuteness and charm.
後悔がうるさい夜だ
Regret makes for a noisy night.
過去は過去だと割り切っちゃえば
If you just write off the past as the past,
きっといいことあるさとか
saying 'surely good things will happen',
それくらい百も承知だ ラッタッタ
I'm fully aware of that much, rattatta.
願うことも
Wishing,
祈ることも
and praying,
許されないから黒く染めた
weren't forgiven, so I dyed it black.
元の色も思い出せない
I can't even remember the original color.
絡んだ運命の
The entangled thread of fate,
糸 糸 糸 糸
thread, thread, thread, thread.
やだ 痛い 痛い 痛い 痛いな
No, it hurts, hurts, hurts, hurts.
悲劇のヒロイン気取っちゃって
Acting like a tragic heroine,
もう嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
I already hate, hate, hate, hate, hate it.
諦めちゃえば
Why don't you just give up?
でも 会いたい たい たい たいな
But I want to see you, see you, see you, see you.
自己回答 こんがらがっちゃって
My self-answer is all tangled up.
明日またきっと壊すけどいいの
I'll surely break it again tomorrow, but that's fine.
トラウマも咲いた詩のです です
Trauma has also bloomed into poetry, desu desu.
ででっでっです
De-de-de-desu.
夢の中で君と
In my dream, with you,
手を繋いでいるの
I'm holding hands.
何も知らない
Knowing nothing,
あの頃の二人のままで
just like the two of us back then.
でも分かっているよ
But I understand,
すぐに覚めてしまうと
that I will wake up soon.
それならばいっそ
If that's the case, then rather,
君の手でそっと
with your hand, gently,
トドメ刺して
finish me off.
ほら 今 今 今！
Look, now, now, now!
やだ 痛い 痛い 痛い 痛いな
No, it hurts, hurts, hurts, hurts.
奇跡とかちょっと望んじゃって
Hoping a little for a miracle,
もう嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
I already hate, hate, hate, hate, hate it.
たちが悪いは
It's nasty.
ねぇ 辛い 辛い 辛い 辛いな
Hey, it's painful, painful, painful, painful.
お菓子とか全部えぐり取って
Scoop out all the sweets,
薄情で結構
Cold-hearted is fine,
好きに呼んでいいよ
call me whatever you like.
トラウマにバイバイしたいのです です
I want to say bye-bye to trauma, desu desu.
ででっでっです
De-de-de-desu.
です
Desu.
ででっでっです
De-de-de-desu.
すいちゃん来てくれてありがとう！
Sui-chan, thank you for coming!
いいえ！するだけで楽しかったぜ！
No way! Just doing it was fun!
いや嬉しいぜ！
I'm so happy!
ジグザグ
ZIG-ZAG
ジグザグ ジグザグ
ZIG-ZAG ZIG-ZAG
ジグザグ ジグザグ ジグザグ
ZIG-ZAG ZIG-ZAG ZIG-ZAG
ジグザグ
ZIG-ZAG
ということで皆さん すいちゃんが来てくれました
So everyone, Sui-chan has come!
来ましたよ
I'm here!
すいちゃんの事あらわすあの原石 バーチャルアイドルの星街すいせいです
That gemstone that represents Sui-chan, I'm the virtual idol Hoshimachi Suisei.
すいちゃんはー！
Sui-chan is...!
今日もかわいい！
Cute today too!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
ということで
So,
ルイ セカンドアルバム発売決定おめでとう！
Lui, congratulations on your 2nd album release!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そう、いっぱい相談しました。
Right, I consulted with her a lot.
いっぱいいっぱい確かに、ルル聞いたかも。なんか曲、結構知ってるかも。
I certainly heard a lot, Lulu. I might actually know the songs quite well.
そう、いっぱいいっぱい相談しましたすいちゃんに。
Yes, I consulted Suichan a lot.
このジグザグもね、実はちょっとリリース前から聴いてて。
Actually, I was listening to this "Zigzag" even before its release.
今日はですね、ジグザグをすいちゃんと歌いたかった理由はですね、ま、本当にあの...
The reason I wanted to sing "Zigzag" with Suichan today is, well, really...
いっぱいいっぱい相談をしたっていうのと...
...because I consulted with her so much, and...
あと曲がね、あのタイトルを一緒にね、考えてくれたんですよね、ジグザグという。
...also, she helped me think of the song title together, "Zigzag".
一番最初タイトル本当は違ったんだよね。
At first, the title was actually different, wasn't it?
そこからどうかなーつって、え、ジグザグってトラウマって意味あるらしいよみたいな。
We were wondering about it, like "Eh, apparently 'zigzag' has a meaning related to trauma."
なって、一緒にね、え、ジグザグ良くない？
And then, together, "Eh, isn't 'Zigzag' good?"
ジグザグじゃない？みたいな、間にハイフンとか入れようぜみたいな。え、お洒落じゃない？みたいな。
"Isn't it 'Zigzag'? Let's put a hyphen in between." "Eh, isn't that stylish?"
たくさんたくさん相談をしまして、でね、ジグザグすいちゃんに合いそうだなーみたいな。
I consulted a lot, and thought "Zigzag" would really suit Suichan.
え、でもこれね、歌っててね、楽しいね。
Eh, but singing this, you know, it's fun.
楽しいでしょ？これ楽しいですよすごい。楽しいんですよ是非皆さんも。
It's fun, isn't it? This is really fun. It's fun, everyone should try it.
ルイとね、やっぱその声質というかね、このなんだろ、低音歌う組というか。
With Lui, like, the voice quality, or how should I put it, the low-tone singing group...
として、なんか合ってるなっていうのもすごい思ったし、なんか歌ってて楽しかったです。
...as that, I really thought we matched well, and it was fun singing.
いやもう、ジグザグ歌うんだったら、すいちゃんと歌いたいって言って。もう、絶対すいちゃんと歌うって言って。
No, I said if I'm singing "Zigzag", I want to sing with Suichan. I said I'll definitely sing with Suichan.
あの、お呼びしたら快諾をしてくださいました。本当にありがとうございます。忙しい中でありがとうございまーす。
When I called her, she readily agreed. Thank you so much. Thank you amidst your busyness.
いえいえ、そんなもうね、生出演なんかもういつでも呼んでください、そんなね。ありがとうございます。
No no, really, for a live appearance, call me anytime. Thank you.
コメントの皆さんもね、はい、どうもどうも。あ、いい、かっこいいかっこいい。合ってる合ってる。
Everyone in the comments too, yes, hello hello. Ah, "Good", "Cool cool". "Matches matches".
いやー本当に一緒に歌えて、ま、本当に緊張したんだけども、一緒に歌えて良かった。しかも2回目なんですよ、一緒に二人で歌ったの。
I'm really glad we could sing together, well, I was really nervous, but I'm glad. Moreover, it's the second time we've sung together.
そうなんですよねー。前はMガデのファーストでね。バグ。
That's right. Before was at M-Garden's 1st live. "Bug".
そう、バグで。今度はジグザグ。次は何になるんでしょうか。何グですか？何グになるんでしょうか。
Yes, with "Bug". This time "Zigzag". What will be next? What-gu is it? What-gu will it be?
はい、どうぞね、今後も楽しみにしていただけたらなと思うんですけれども。
Yes, please look forward to the future.
なんとまだ告知があるんです。えー、そんなまさか。
Actually, there is still an announcement. Eh, no way.
なので... え、ちょっとこのアルバムに絡めたやつですよ。
So... eh, it's something related to this album.
えー、何何？気になる気になるー。
Eh, what what? I'm curious, I'm curious.
気になる？じゃあ一緒に見ようか。え、見るんだ。そう、一緒に見よ。ということで、こちらをご覧ください。どうぞ。
Curious? Then shall we watch together? Eh, we're watching it. Yes, let's watch together. So, please watch this. Go ahead.
さてさて、存じ上げな... え？わ？
Well then, I don't know... Eh? Wha?
Who are you you you どちら様？
Who are you, you, you, who are you?
Face to face こんにちは
Face to face, hello.
You and me も乗ってだって Upside down for
You and me riding along, Upside down for...
自分自分 Look a lie? Like a lie?
Myself, myself. Look a lie? Like a lie?
構えて構えて構えは誰気な 自分は自分ので
Get ready, get ready, whose stance is that? I'll do it my way...
片付けましょう
Let's clean this up.
で、Foo Are you 誰？
So, Foo Are you, who?
なんと、セカンドアルバムより、『Foo Are!?』が本日24時に先行デジタルリリースがされますー！
Surprisingly, from the 2nd album, "Foo Are!?" will be digitally released in advance today at 24:00!
誰？誰？誰？こっちのルイはわかるけど、こっちのルイは誰？誰なんだろう。
Who? Who? Who? I know this Lui, but who is this Lui? Who could it be?
気になるねー。実はこの曲作った人も気にならない？
Curious, huh. Actually, aren't you curious about the person who made this song too?
なんと魔眼ウインクを作ってくれた、テニヲハさんが今回も作成してくれたよー！あー、テニヲハ節確かに感じる！
Surprisingly, Tenioha-san, who made "Magan Wink", created this one too! Ah, I certainly feel the Tenioha style!
感じるよね。感じる感じる、めっちゃ感じる。そしてこの配信終了後には、MVが公開されます！
You feel it, right? Feel it, feel it, really feel it. And after this stream ends, the MV will be released!
わー、MVさっき流れてたやつですか？そうなんですよ。なんと、高嶺ルイ史上初のオリジナルアニメMV、フルアニメMVを作らせていただきました。
Wow, is it the MV that was playing just now? That's right. Surprisingly, I was allowed to make Takane Lui's first ever original full anime MV.
わーお、すごかった。めっちゃぬるぬる動いてた。ぬるぬる動いてたでしょ？しかも、なんか私が好きそうな絵のタッチじゃない？
Wow, that was amazing. It was moving so smoothly. Smoothly, right? And, isn't it an art style I'd seem to like?
あー、確かにね。なんと私ですね、すごいもう予てよりMV作っていただきたいなと思っていた、安田現象さんに...
Ah, certainly. Surprisingly, I... I've been thinking for a long time that I wanted him to make an MV, Yasuda Gensho-san...
あの？あの安田現象さんですか？そうです。大丈夫ですか？現象さんですか？そうですね、大丈夫ですか？
That? That Yasuda Gensho-san? Yes. Are you okay? Gensho-san? Yes, are you okay?
作成をしていただいたフルアニメーションMVとなっております。
It's a fully animated MV created just for this.
わあ、すごい！サムネも可愛い！
Wow, amazing! The thumbnail is cute too!
可愛いでしょ？アッカンベーしてます。
Cute, right? I'm doing an 'akanbe'.
アッカンベーしてるね。
You are doing an 'akanbe'.
ということでこのね、「誰」というのは、内面にいる...
So, about this 'Who'... it's about the one inside...
まあ私... 私けっこう内面にアンチ持ってるんですけど。
Well, I actually have quite the 'anti' inside myself.
あ、そうなんだ。自分ので？
Oh, is that so? Your own?
そう、鷹嶺ルイのアンチを持ってるんですけど。
Yes, I have an anti of Takane Lui inside me.
「お前本当にこれできんのか？」みたいなね。
Like, 'Can you really do this?'
おお。
Oh.
「お前本当にやれんのか？」みたいな。
Like, 'Are you really gonna pull this off?'
そう... え、このなんか感情とか誰なん？みたいな。
So... like, 'Who is this feeling coming from?'
おお。
Oh.
うん。お... え、私なの？なんで私、私を否定してるの？みたいな。
Yeah. Like... 'Wait, is it me? Why am I denying myself?'
そういうね... 深い... 「誰」っていう...
It's that kind of... deep... 'Who'...
へえー！
Heeh!
そういう楽曲に仕上がっておりますし。
That's how the song turned out.
てか怖い言う、誰？
Wait, that sounds scary. Who?
誰？誰なの？私なの？
Who? Who is it? Is it me?
誰なんの？ふふふ。
Who is it? Fufufu.
という、えー、曲になっておりますので...
So, uh, that's the kind of song it is...
これからちょっとMVもね、あのプレミア公開させていただきますので...
I'll be doing a premiere release of the MV shortly as well...
ぜひぜひ楽しんでいただければなと思いますし。
So I hope you all enjoy it.
けっこう耳に残るサウンドになってますのでね。
It has a sound that really sticks in your ears.
ねえ、もう今後ろでイントロ流れてますけど...
Right? The intro is already playing in the background...
え、ほら早くフル聴きたいし...
I want to hear the full version soon...
もうなんなら今から歌ってもらえませんか？
Actually, could you just sing it for us now?
え？一緒に歌いますか？
Eh? Will you sing with me?
え、あ... うんと... ﾁｬﾁｬﾁｬ... うーん... HEY！... はい。
Eh, ah... um... Cha-cha-cha... hmm... HEY! ...Yes.
ちょっと歌えなそうですね。
Seems like you can't sing it.
ちょっとダメだ。
Yeah, no good.
ということでこの後、実は「誰」を...
So, right after this, actually...
先行で歌わせていただきます！
I'll be singing 'DARE' ahead of the release!
えー！わあー！
Eeeh! Waaah!
そうなの！？
Is that so!?
あ、じゃあ私は端から見てますということで...
Ah, then I'll be watching from the side...
え、待っててね。
Eh, wait for me okay?
あのご飯食べよ。
Um, let's eat.
ご飯食べよ一緒に。
Let's eat together.
あ、分かった分かった。じゃ舞台袖で見てますわ。
Ah, okay okay. I'll watch from the wings then.
あ、この後、じゃあご飯ということで。よろしくお願いします。
Ah, so food afterwards then. looking forward to it.
てか、Who are you... 誰？
Wait, Who are you... Who?
じゃ！
See ya!
あ、ありがとー！
Ah, thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
すいちゃんでした！ありがとうみんな！
That was Sui-chan! Thanks everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、えー、心強かった助っ人...
So, uh, my reassuring helper...
すいちゃんもいなくなり、私一人でですね...
Sui-chan has left, and now I'm alone...
えー、新曲「ラピスラズリ」にも入っております曲...
Uh, a song included in the new release 'Lapis Lazuli'...
「誰」を歌わせていただきます。
I will sing 'DARE'.
ちょっと水飲んでいいですか？
Can I drink some water first?
水飲みますよ。
I'm gonna drink water.
水飲みます。
Drinking water.
はい！
Okay!
ということで、戻って参りました。
Alright, I'm back.
それでは皆さん、聴いてください。
So then everyone, please listen.
「誰」
'DARE'
誰だ 誰 そちら様 どちら様
Who is it? Who? You there, who are you?
はてさてと Who are you? How are you?
Well now, Who are you? How are you?
お元気で 一足お先に
Take care, I'm going on ahead.
てか Who are you? How are you?
I mean, Who are you? How are you?
お元気で...
Take care...
一足お先に
...I'm going on ahead.
てか Who are you?
I mean, Who are you?
昨日の自分が描いた円から はみ出さないように
So as not to step out of the circle drawn by yesterday's self,
ひと回り小さな円を 描くような
Like drawing a circle one size smaller.
ボールのバウンドが少しずつ 低くなる様を
Watching the bounce of a ball get lower little by little,
術もなく 眺めているような気分でしょ
Feeling like you're watching it helplessly, right?
ところで貴方...
By the way, you...
DARE!?
WHO!?
誰 誰 誰
Who, who, who?
存じ上げないわ
I don't know you.
誰 誰 誰 存じ上げないわ
Who, who, who? I don't know you.
Who are you you you you どちら様
Who are you, you, you, you? Who is this?
Face to face こんにちは
Face to face, hello.
You & Me もなってたって Upside down for 自分 自分
You & Me become Upside down for myself, myself.
Look-alike? Not-alike? Like-or-Like?
通りゃんせ
You may pass.
てかまえ てかまえ てかまえは DARE!?
Wait, who's in front? In front? The one in front is WHO!?
昨日の自分は自分の手で 片付けましょう
Let's finish off yesterday's self with our own hands.
てか Who are you?
I mean, Who are you?
誰？
Who?
Look-alike
Look-alike la-ka-la-ka-la kami?
Look-alike la-ka-la-ka-la god?
Look-alike
つーかさ 確かに私が 私のこと見張り続けてる
I mean, certainly I am constantly watching over myself.
なのでクッと 背筋伸ばし 微笑むの
So I straighten my back with a jerk and smile.
徒花 誰に見られずとも 美しく咲くと言うけど
They say fleeting flowers bloom beautifully unseen by anyone,
風や虫にもそっぽ向かれたら 咲き方を改めるだろう
But if even the wind and insects turn away, you'd change how you bloom, right?
誰？
Who?
存じ上げないわ... 誰？
I don't know you... Who?
Who are you you you you どちら様
Who are you, you, you, you? Who is this?
Face to face こんばんは
Face to face, good evening.
You & Me もなってたって Upside down for 自分 自分
You & Me become Upside down for myself, myself.
Look-alike? Not-alike? Look-a-look-a-like?
通りゃんせ
You may pass.
倒したの私よ
I'm the one who defeated myself.
私を倒せ
Defeat me.
的確 Are you? How are you?
Precise. Are you? How are you?
How about you? 誰？
How about you? Who are you?
Look at like a...
Look at laka laka laka me
誰だ 誰
Who is it? Who?
そちら様
Who are you?
どちら様
Who goes there?
はてさてと
Well then...
これは誰だ
Who is this?
誰であれ
Whoever it is,
見せつけるだけ
I'll just show them what I've got.
Good luck my dear
Have a nice day
はいということで
Okay, so with that,
今日のライブは
today's live concert...
これにて終了となります
ends right here.
皆さん本当にありがとうございました
Thank you all so much!
改めて告知をさせていただきます
Let me make the announcements again.
セカンドアルバム『Lapis Lazuli』が
My 2nd Album 'Lapis Lazuli'...
12月3日に発売されます
will be released on December 3rd!
えー予約は、えーもうできますので
Uh, reservations are... you can reserve it now,
こちらかな？
over here, maybe?
こちらから是非是非予約をしてください
Please, please make your reservations from here.
もうすごく頑張った
I really worked hard...
えー楽曲...
on the songs...
頑張って頑張って歌った楽曲ばかりになりますので
It's full of songs I sang with all my might,
是非是非早く皆さんに聴いていただきたいなと思いますので
so I really want you all to hear them as soon as possible.
是非セカンドアルバムもよろしくお願いします
Please support my 2nd Album too!
そして、豪華なスライドボックスパッケージで
Also, it comes in a gorgeous slide-box package,
イラストブックや缶バッジ
with an illustration book, can badge,
直筆サイン入りのジャケットカードなどが付いてくる完全生産限定盤
and a hand-signed jacket card in the 'Completely Limited Production Edition'.
そしてランダムアナザージャケット全5種から1枚
And with one random 'Another Jacket' out of 5 types,
数量限定ランダムで直筆サインとメッセージが付く通常盤
the 'Regular Edition' may include a limited random hand-signed message.
各種法人特典も盛りだくさんでございます
There are plenty of store-specific bonuses as well.
秋葉原ゲーマーズ本店さんにてリリース記念のミニライブもやる予定でございます
We also plan to hold a release commemorative mini-live at Akihabara Gamers main store.
そして、先程歌いました
And, the song I just sang,
『DARE!?』が本日24時にデジタルリリースされますし
'DARE!?' will be released digitally at 24:00 today,
このあとすぐフルアニメーションMVも公開されます
and the full animation MV will premiere right after this.
えーこのままね見ていただければ
If you keep watching like this...
えー自動で...
Uh, automatically...
確か... 確か自動で！
I think... I think it redirects automatically!
MVに飛びますので
You'll jump to the MV,
是非是非フルアニメーション、あの、私自身初のフルアニメーションになっておりますので
so please watch it! It's my very first full animation video.
是非可愛く仕上がったので見ていただけると嬉しいでございます
It turned out really cute, so I'd be happy if you watched it.
はい、えー今回...
Yes, so this time...
あの、重大告知ライブということで
Since it was titled 'Major Announcement Live',
皆さんね、あのソロライブなんじゃないかって
everyone was guessing, 'Is it a solo live?'
すごいあの予想をしてくださっていたんですけれども
You were all predicting that so much, but...
私はですね、まだあのソロライブは、あの決まっておりません
For me... the solo live hasn't been decided yet.
ですがですね、私あの音楽をやりたいと心に決めてからですね
However! Since I decided in my heart that I wanted to do music,
えー夢であるファーストアルバムがリリースできたり
I was able to release my dream 1st Album,
そしてファーストアルバムを皆さんが買ってくださったから
and because everyone bought that 1st Album,
えーこうやってセカンドアルバムを全国流通として
I'm able to release this 2nd Album...
えー発売することができました
with nationwide distribution like this.
えー一千万再生のMVを
Uh, having two MVs...
が二つもできましたし
with 10 million views,
その他の楽曲もたくさんたくさんみんなに愛してもらって
and having all my other songs loved by so many of you,
えー再生数もすごい伸びて
with the view counts growing so much...
もうみんなのおかげでですね、私あのこんなにあの音楽をやっていてよかったなと
It's all thanks to you that I feel so glad I'm doing music.
今でも、えーそしてこれからもきっと想うと思います
I feel that now, and I'm sure I'll keep feeling that way.
えーソロライブ
Uh, a solo live...
次はですね、えー夢を一つずつ叶えてきたからこそ
Next... because I've made my dreams come true one by one,
次はもう
the next step...
ソロライブしかないやろ！
has to be a solo live, right!?
なので、えー必ず、えー皆さんと一緒にソロライブを
So, I definitely want to dream of a solo live together with you,
えー夢見て、みんなと一緒にまたここから走り出したいなと思います
and start running from here together with everyone again.
えー是非是非皆さん、えーファーストに引き続きセカンドアルバムも
So everyone, please, following the 1st, pick up the 2nd Album too.
えーお手元に取っていただけると嬉しいです
I'd be happy if you could get your hands on it.
なので、えーこれからまた鷹嶺ルイと一緒に
So, from now on, together with Takane Lui,
ソロライブを目指しましょう
let's aim for a solo live!
目指してくれますか？
Will you aim for it with me?
ん？
Hm?
目指してくれるか？
Will you aim for it with me?
もちろん！ えーありがとう！
Of course! Aww, thank you!
はい、もう本当にみんなの、えー力がないと私はえー
Yes, really, without everyone's power,
きっとソロライブに、えー到達できないと思うので
I surely won't be able to reach a solo live.
私も頑張りますが、みんなも一緒に走り続けていただけると嬉しいです
I'll do my best, but I'd be happy if you all kept running with me.
えーLui友のみんな、そして
To all my Lui-tomo, and...
ルイのことはまぁ2番手3番手ぐらいに推してるよというみんな
those of you who have Lui as your 2nd or 3rd favorite,
そして、えーホロリスの皆さん
and all the Holo-listeners,
そしてこれからまた出会うであろう、えータカネルイを知っていただける皆さん
and to everyone I'll meet from now on who gets to know Takane Lui...
えー皆さんの協力が必要ですんで、是非是非よろしくお願いします
I need everyone's cooperation, so please, I'm counting on you!
これからもよろしくお願いします
Please continue to support me.
はい、ということで
Okay, so...
じゃあ次のね
For the next one...
ま、次重大告知がある時には
Next time there's a major announcement,
もう超重大告知としてね
as a super major announcement,
ソロライブが発表できるように
I'll work hard so I can announce a solo live.
これからもがんばります
I'll keep doing my best.
みんな本当に今日はありがとう！
Everyone, truly, thank you for today!
セカンドアルバム楽しみにしててね
Please look forward to the 2nd album.
これからどんどん情報が出てくると思いますので
I think more info will be coming out soon,
お楽しみにー
so look forward to it!
またねー！
See you later!